The storm is over now, the static's gone Right
here is where you've been all along Your voice
was lost, your world was grey We're here to chase
the dark away You walked through fire, you
walked through rain But you will never walk
alone again
We are your sanctuary in the storm A fire here to
keep you safe and warm Inside this circle held so
tight We'll be your true and gentle light So let
the painted smile fall down You're standing on
your native ground Your home
You're finally home
The last few words on the floor You don't need it
anymore The silence has no power here We'll
banish every single fear Just let it go The heavy
load at the ending of this lonely road Just lean
on us, we'll hold the line Your broken heart will
mend, we'll tell
We are your sanctuary and your storm
A father here to keep you safe and warm Inside
this circle held so tight Will be your true and
gentle light So let the painted smile fall down
You're standing on your native ground You're
home
You're finally home
You're home You're
fine
We are your sanctuary You're not alone